In the great sea of Ignora lay
five islands in the shape of a cross.
Four pointed in each cardinal direction
around a larger one in the center
to form Ente Isla, the islands
watched over by the gods.
All who lived in Ente Isla
knew of Satan, ruler of demons.
His very name was synonymous
with the terror and cruelty
which ruled this demon realm
teeming with creatures of the night.
Satan's ambition was to
conquer the human world
and build there a land of peace and
prosperity for all night's creatures.
He had four trusted generals:
Adramelech, Lucifer, Alciel, and Malacoda.
These four great demons launched
attacks on the four continents.
However, a lone hero rose up
against them, sacred sword in hand.
Along with a band of comrades, the hero
crushed Lucifer's army to the west.
They went on to defeat Adramelech in
the north and Malacoda in the south,
and then the federation
of knights led by this hero
invaded the central continent, where
the lord of demons kept his castle.
Damn! You wretched humans!
Divine souls, gather in the realm of the
dead. Stop the demons and drag them to the netherworld!
What?!
How dare you!
Sire!
Out of my way!
I am sorry, Sire.
The human forces are
steadily overcoming my army.
lt is only a matter
of time before this castle falls.
I never
dreamed a single human "hero"
could force
us into such dire straits...
Sire,
I suggest we withdraw for
now and regroup.
Hear me, humans!
I shall leave
Ente Isla in your hands today!
But know this: I shall return
to subjugate
you and all of Ente Isla!
The Devil Arrives in Sasazuka
Where are we?!
-Are you all right, Sire?
Alciel, the first thing
we must do is find a place to heal.
Yes, Sire.
But this seems
an awfully noisy place...
Wh-What is this world?!
Could it...
Sire?! Why
do you take that form?!
What?
These are...
...human hands?
Calm yourself, Alciel.
We must be
careful not to use magic.
Excuse me, you there!
Could I talk to you for a minute?
Do not speak to
me so familiarly, lowly human!
Do you wish to die?
Uh-oh, they're foreigners.
Okay, do you boys understand Japanese?
You look injured. Were you in a fight?
Why?! Even if
they do not speak our language,
I am a demon, a user of magic...
Alciel.
Do not use your magic now.
Not until we learn of this world.
Aren't they hot, dressed like that?
They're "cosplaying," Sir. Don't see
that much in this neighborhood, though.
This is Sasaki on patrol duty. I've got
some boys with minor injuries here.
This seems to be a carriage...
The victims are foreigners
from somewhere in Asia.
We're in west Shinjuku, area 1-20.
But it doesn't require horses...
Not sure whether they're
tourists or residents.
lt doesn't
seem to be powered by magic...
Now, can I get you to join us
in the car? If nothing's wrong...
Do not presume
to touch me, lowly human!
Know your
place, you inferior creature!
Okay, you two behave yourselves.
Um, this is katsudon, okay?
Katsu... don...
Yes, yes.
They coated animal flesh in some
sort of grain and fried it in hot oil.
Then they put a mashed-up bird egg on top,
and heated it even further
in a fish broth...
I'm not actually supposed to feed you,
but you two are injured,
so we'll just call it my treat.
I want more
information about this world.
What? Oh, yes.
Answer my questions.
Alciel.
Alciel?
Satan!
H-Hey, you can't just come in here!
Silence.
Y-Yes, Sir...
King Satan...
I'm so glad you're all right.
I used hypnotism to gain
some information about this world...
Apparently we've come to
a world called "Earth."
We're in one of its nations,
an archipelago called "Japan."
We stand now in its capital of "Tokyo,"
and this building is someplace
called a "police station."
The police are evidently a state
institution which maintains public order.
I see. And what is that
substance on the table?
"Katsu Doon." It's an extremely
common food in this country.
"Katsu Doon"...
Yes, that has a powerful ring to it.
This is of great interest.
What? N-No, it's not
particularly important.
In this world, things like spell-casting,
magic, demons, and the Devil
are considered fantasies...
things that don't really exist.
Magic doesn't exist?! How could that be?!
I see, so the insufficient magic here
left us unable to retain our demonic forms?
Yes. But who would have thought we'd
look like this stripped of our magic...
Perhaps humans actually form
the basis of all living creatures.
You jest, Sire.
I'm sure it's merely an effect
of this world and the Gate.
I still retain some of my magic.
It's quite an effort to stem
its outward flow, though.
What about you, Alciel?
King Satan, is this?
No, I highly doubt you
conjured this with magic.
Oh.
If I adjust the amount of magic
I release, I won't run out for a while.
The real problem is that we
have no way to amass more.
Still, if Earth is familiar with the
concept of magic, even as "imaginary,"
there may be some method
of recovering our powers.
The path left to us is to discover
that method and get them back.
Until then, we have no choice
but to live in this world
and obey these humans' rules.
What a cruel reality this is.
Yes. Our first step is...
to obtain "records" and "certificates
of residence" at this "ward office."
Sire...
H-Hmm?
Here.
"Sadao Maou"
"Head of Household"
All right. Next, we create
accounts at the "bank."
To do so, we use this.
What is that paper?
It's this country's currency.
I borrowed it from that police person.
We also need a seal.
I whipped one up for myself.
Most impressive.
"Lifelong Safe Trust"
"Super Fixed Deposit"
Here you are.
Good. Now we just need to secure
a base of operations from a "real-tore."
Realtor
We are searching house!
What sort of home do you have in mind, Sir?
He understood you!
C-Calm down, Alciel!
A little language
acquisition is nothing for me!
O-Okay! I'm in the groove here!
The landlady here is a
very admirable person.
If I may speak frankly,
she says she wants to set an example
by taking on persons of
unknown background, like you.
Th-This is...
Yes. Even I can tell...
Well, at least
it's a two-story house...
And it has six rooms.
You'd be renting room 201 here.
We get one room?
I suppose we
should be grateful it has a roof...
Certainly when you compare
it to the Devil's Castle, it's a bit...
Good afternoon.
ls it... human?
You two are the new rental
applicants, correct?
lt spoke?!
This is the apartment owner.
She lives next door.
I am Miki Shiba.
That's "Miki" spelled with the
kanji for "beauty" and "radiance."
Oh, but do feel free to call me "Mikitty."
Right...
Sire, are you sure this is
the right place for us?
It seems that in this world
they say "patience is a virtue."
This style of Devil's Castle
will make a nice change.
Oh, Sire...
From here, we shall take
a new step... for... ward...
King Satan! King Satan!
King Satan!
Central Police
Hospital
I didn't realize this body required food!
It is a human body, Sire.
Not to mention that "IV drip" thing
cost a full month's rent on the castle!
You know what they call that here?
"Rubbing salt into a wound"!
Sire, that uncanny landlady
spared us a good deal of trouble.
She tells me that Japan requires
residents to carry health ins...
Anyway! Money is clearly of
the essence in this human society.
I can't afford to expend any
more of my magic, either.
Which means we have only one choice left.
What is that, Sire?
Whoops, I did it wrong.
You idiot! Résumé forms
don't grow on trees, you know!
Okay, I'm "Sadao Maou"...
"Shiro Ashiya" ...Do you think
this name is strange, Sire?
It's too late to ask me that!
We already made IDs!
King Satan.
Yeah?
Might I suggest you put a little
more thought into your spending?
I'm thinking plenty!
Summer's coming, so we need a fridge,
and owning a laundry machine is
cheaper than coin laundry in the long run.
The bike is essential
for commuting to work.
That's not the issue, Sire!
I'm questioning why you
didn't pay in installments.
I hate loans.
Now look here...
And installment plans
come with fees, you know!
I ain't paying for something
I can't touch with my own hands!
In that case, let me ask you this:
How are we supposed to make it to payday
on milk, konjac jelly, and cucumbers?!
Well...
It's not like we've got no money left!
I've still got some in my wallet!
And hey, they give me meals at work!
We'll die.
You propose we eat burgers and fries
three times a day until payday?!
What is this, Super Size Me?
You plan to eat a high-calorie,
high-cholesterol diet from a young age?
I look forward to ten years from now!
I just hope you don't die prematurely of a
lifestyle-related illness before we get home!
I must apologize for my cowardice, Sire,
but you're the one who
argued for biding our time!
You of all people ought to prize constant
diligence and health maintenance!
Put a sock in it! I'm going to work!
Wait, Sire!
Lecture me later!
No, I mean you forgot your umbrella!
Let's go, Dullahan!
Well, I suppose I'll get ready too.
Here.
Please, use this.
Er, um...
I work right nearby.
At the MgRonald's by the train station.
All right...
I don't even care if you throw it out!
Yeesh, that's cold!
This week is key! It decides who sells the
most of our feature item in our district!
I swear, I will break the sales
record for black pepper fries!
Welcome to MgRonald's.
May I take your order?
A cheeseburger and a small cola.
May I interest you in some black pepper
fries? They're our featured item.
No, thanks.
- Yes, these little continuous efforts are
necessary - One cheeseburger and one small cola...
- for my eventual comeback as lord of demons!
- That will be 220 yen.
- For my eventual comeback as lord of demons!
- Here's 1,000.
Let me get your change.
That's one chicken burger, one
iced coffee, and one Happiness Meal.
730 yen, please!
Oh, would you like to use
our microwave, Ma'am?
If you've brought baby food
that can go in the microwave,
I'll heat it up while you wait.
You're sure you wouldn't mind?
My pleasure, Ma'am.
Mr. Maou, you're really amazing!
I can't believe you thought
of her baby food, even!
Oh, that.
Accommodating our customers'
needs when we have the time
gives us a long-term advantage.
You're so cool! You're
like a real working adult!
Er, well, it is only a part-time job...
Central
Library
Another job lost, Ashiya.
Please call me "Alciel," Sire.
Anyway, our goal is to return
to Ente Isla, not to do day labor!
As you say, Sire.
You find us a way to get back our magic.
Sire?
I'll work and earn us money.
You use your brains.
This world knows the concepts
of magic and spell-casting.
Maybe if we trace them to their source...
You believe we'll be able
to recover our powers?!
Yes. And then we won't stop at Ente Isla.
I say we rule this world, too!
Sire!
You mean "Maou."
As you wish, Sire. I, Alciel, vow to
discover the path to your supremacy!
Rise, Alciel. You're embarrassing me.
Utopias of
the World
And yet...
Hey! I got a 100-yen-per-hour raise!
Listen, the guy who started
today is pretty good!
Reference
Book Use Only No Private Studying
You're at the bottom of
the totem pole, Sire!
If the Devil is an underling,
what does that make me?!
Not that I've made progress
on this front either...
Peru's Nazca
Lines Egypt's Pyramids England's Stonehenge
And with only books to go on,
all I can do is speculate...
Oh, an earthquake.
Mr. Maou, it's an earthquake.
Yes, yes it is.
Hey, Chi.
Yes?
Everyone makes mistakes.
But it's the sixth time I've dropped
fries on the floor this month!
True, you do drop them every other day.
I just clean up after myself while
everybody else waits on customers...
At this rate potatoes will
start sprouting from the floor!
Hey, you kids on break.
What's wrong, Chi?
What's wrong, Manager?
Call me "Miss Kisaki"!
It's getting crowded out there.
When your breaks are up,
I want you operating at full power.
This is when the fight for
♪1 really gets in gear.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, and try not to plant
too many potatoes, Sasaki.
Yes, Ma'am.
- One MgBurger meal with black pepper fries!
- One order of large black pepper fries, please!
Welcome to MgRonald's.
A smile, please!
W-Welcome to MgRonald's...
If we keep this up, we can do it!
We can make ♪1 in the district!
They're not done yet?
Don't tell me the fryer's broken?!
Did it have to be the black pepper fryer?!
Okay, Maou, focus! What now?
If I don't do something,
making ♪1 is the least of our problems!
Do I use my magic?
Please save your magic
for emergencies, Sire.
What's wrong?
Life is fail.
It's not your fault, Mr. Maou.
And the repairman should
be done by evening!
Hey, Maa, got a second?
Yeah.
What's going on? Is she gonna
blame me for us not getting ♪1?
No, it's not like I broke it...
Or does she suspect me because
I was about to use magic?!
Thanks for waiting! Here we go.
At ease, kid. It's not bad news.
I just got the approval
from the district office.
Uh, what?
Sadao Maou, as of today,
I'm promoting you to A-level staff.
All right!
I'm A-level staff, Ashiya! I got a raise!
Hey.
Huh? Oh, it's you.
I went to your restaurant after we spoke.
Oh, you did? I didn't see you.
You should've said something!
I watched you all day from
the bookstore across the street.
You look so different that
I thought I was mistaken, but...
You started to cast a spell.
A spell?
Wait, are you...?!
Why exactly are you working
part-time at MgRonald's, Satan?!
Emilia the hero?!
Where will morning start
from, in this quiet sky?
Fingertips twining in a pinky
swear I pretended not to see
If the moon's been laughed at,
she'll sink away toward yesterday
Liar, coward... if I'm
all these things at once
Then I only blossomed in dreams
I hid in the moon's shadow,
but the truth is, I was crying
The tears won't flow anymore...
did they all dry up?
If I could forgive everything,
maybe they'd flow again
But these are all things I want to protect
The Hero
Stays at the Devil's Castle for Work Reasons